entropay.com 2017-12-27

# Entropay | Privacy Policy

Last modified: Seventh of February 2017 (07/02/2017 - UK date format)

Ixaris Systems Limited ("We") are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

This policy (together with our terms of use at [](https://secure2.entropay.com/static/pages/terms.general.html)[](https://www.entropay.com/website-terms-of-use)<https://www.entropay.com/website-terms-of-use> and any other documents referred to on it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. By visiting [https://www.entropay.com](https://www.entropay.com/) (our site) you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this policy.

For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the  **Act** ), the data controller is Ixaris Systems Limited of 10 Midford Place, London, W1T 5AE, United Kingdom.

## Information we may collect from you

We may collect and process the following data about you:

  * **Information you give us.**  You may give us information about you by filling in forms on our site or by corresponding with us by phone, e-mail or otherwise. This includes information you provide when you register to use our site, subscribe to our service, or open an account and when you report a problem with our site. The information you give us may include your name, address, e-mail address and phone number, personal description, financial and credit or debit card information.
  *  **Information we collect about you.**  With regard to each of your visits to our site we may automatically collect the following information:
    * technical information, including the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, your login information, browser type and version, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform;
    * information about your visit, including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through and from our site (including date and time); products you viewed or searched for; page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page and any phone number used to call our customer service number.
  *  **Information we receive from other sources.**  We may receive information about you if you use any of the other websites we operate or the other services we provide. We are also working closely with third parties (including, for example, business partners, sub-contractors in technical, payment and delivery services, advertising networks, analytics providers, search information providers, credit reference agencies) and may receive information about you from them.

## Tracking technologies

Technologies such as cookies, beacons, tags and scripts or similar technologies are used by Ixaris Systems Limited and it's partners on its online services.

We may use Cookies for a variety of purposes and to enhance your online experience, for example, by remembering your log-in status and viewing preferences from a previous use of an online service, for when you later return to that online service.

For more information on the types of Cookies that are used by our services refer to our Cookie Policy which is available at: [](https://secure2.entropay.com/static/pages/cookieSettings.html)<https://www.entropay.com/entropay-cookie-policy>.

Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use cookies or similar technologies in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to opt out of interest-based advertising click here: <http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/> (or if located in the European Union click here <http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/>). Please note you will continue to receive generic ads.

## Analytics/Log Files

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We do not link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about you.

## Uses made of the information

We use information held about you in the following ways:

  * **Information you give to us.**  We will use this information:
    * to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us and to provide you with the information, products and services that you request from us;
    * to provide you with information about other goods and services we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about;
    * to provide you, or permit selected third parties to provide you, with information about goods or services we feel may interest you. If you are an existing customer, we will only contact you by electronic means (e-mail or SMS) with information about goods and services similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale or negotiations of a sale to you. If you are a new customer, and where we permit selected third parties to use your data, we (or they) will contact you by electronic means only if you have consented to this. If you do not want us to use your data in this way, or to pass your details on to third parties for marketing purposes, please tick the relevant box on the form on which we collect your data;
    * to notify you about changes to our service; you may also choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails, accessing the email preferences in your account settings page, or you can contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#fd8e888d8d928f89bd9893898f928d9c84d39e9290).
    * to ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.
  *  **Information we collect about you.**  We will use this information:
    * to administer our site and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes;
    * to improve our site to ensure that content is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer;
    * to allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so;
    * as part of our efforts to keep our site safe and secure;
    * to measure or understand the effectiveness of advertising we serve to you and others, and to deliver relevant advertising to you;
    * to make suggestions and recommendations to you and other users of our site about goods or services that may interest you or them.
  *  **Information we receive from other sources.**  We may combine this information with information you give to us and information we collect about you. We may use this information and the combined information for the purposes set out above (depending on the types of information we receive).

## Disclosure of your information

We may share your personal information with any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006. We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy or otherwise notified to you. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

We may share your information with selected third parties including:

  * Business partners, suppliers and sub-contractors for the performance of any contract we enter into with them or you. These companies are authorized to use your personal information  _only as necessary to provide_  these services to us.
  * Advertisers and advertising networks that require the data to select and serve relevant adverts to you and others. We do not disclose information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers, but we may provide them with aggregate information about our users (for example, we may inform them that 500 men aged under 30 have clicked on their advertisement on any given day). We may also use such aggregate information to help advertisers reach the kind of audience they want to target (for example, women in SW1). We may make use of the personal data we have collected from you to enable us to comply with our advertisers' wishes by displaying their advertisement to that target audience.
  * Analytics and search engine providers that assist us in the improvement and optimisation of our site.
  * Credit reference agencies for the purpose of assessing your credit score where this is a condition of us entering into a contract with you.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

  * In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.
  * If Ixaris Systems Limited or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.
  * In certain situations, Ixaris Systems Limited may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities. If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation and/or process, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use or terms and conditions of supply and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Ixaris Systems Limited our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

## Where we store your personal data

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, the fulfillment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Any payment transactions or transmission of sensitive information such as credit card and bank account numbers will be encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL). Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

## Your rights

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us as indicated on our Site.

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

## Access to information

The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

Upon request Ixaris Systems Limited will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, amend, delete/remove by emailing our Customer Support at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#abd8dedbdbc4d9dfebcec5dfd9c4dbcad285c8c4c6) or by contacting us by postal mail at the contact information listed below. We will respond to your request within two (2) business days.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

## Social media widgets

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button [and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site]. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

## Single sign-on

You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our privacy policy.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.

## Contact

Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to: 

Entropay Services Limited   
The Penthouse — Suite 1   
Capital Business Center   
Triq Taz-Zwejt   
San Gwann SGN 3000   
Malta   
[[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#d5a6a0a5a5baa7a195b0bba1a7baa5b4acfbb6bab8).
